winnou.net 2010-11-02

# Winnou - School and College Management Software, Hyderabad - Privacy Policy

**Effective Jan 2008**

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the winnou.com website. On some pages you may be requested to submit information to receive information materials or contact us. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

      Name  
      Address  
      Email address  
      Phone number

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing a request to meet your request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the request.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. We will occassionaly send you updated product information and will provide you an opportunity to unsubscribe such informational email alerts.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information from google analytics and such other website traffic monitoring tools to better design our website

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending an email to [info@winnou.com.](mailto:info@winnou.com.) We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at +91.40.23264404 or send us an email at [info@winnou.com.](mailto:info@winnou.com.)
